Cameron Chamberlain

0431 993 870

hi@camjc.com

camjc.com

Web Designer

Offering a first class honours degree in Visual Arts, university level teaching experience in web design, media and research units, as well as both formal and tacit knowledge from client work over the last four years. Utilising education and passion for design to provide the strategy, layout and implementation necessary to provide great experiences across all platforms and drive profitability.

Education

Australian National University

2011

- Bachelor of Visual Arts Honours
- Achieved First Class Honours
- ANU Honours Scholarship awarded

Australian National University

2008-2010

- Bachelor of Visual Arts (Digital Media)
- Average grade of High Distinction

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

2007

• Certificate IV in Animation for Games and Film

Employment

CamJC, Freelance Web Designer	2009-Present
University of Canberra, Sessional Tutor	2011–2013
Australian National University, Technical Officer	2010
Dick Smith Electronics, Sales Assistant	2007–2011

Skills

Technical – HTML5, responsive CSS3 including preprocessors and frameworks, jQuery, JavaScript, API integration, Content Management Systems (WordPress, Textpattern), Jekyll, integration with PHP & Rails.

Design – colour theory, grid systems, typography, communication, research, animation, drawing, photography.